Welcome Taurus, first of all tell
me the market outlook and watch for half an hour best
president and one or two or three days
after that it is solid but still stay here for a while that
I will definitely make a profit of 50,000
and looked into subscribe video
subscribe and like people this
dollar is going to go and if anything then please click on the like button so that
I cut Bandhan Bank very hard
5558 along with that 670 67th class
result first book some profit 3
percent has come you will also remember 3536
sarees so that click there
Tata Power has become a little there
Facebook has become 3 2010
click there and Godrej Properties 1429
Vidya But that I still think that the
target of substances will come now if you say then I have
two times one on you if you say then I have
one oil as soon as I smell it believe me first
two bike wise so friends bye-bye
Tata Consumer Lighting and Consumer Affairs
and when because a little profit-taking will
come in the bank  593 phase privacy I will give
dreams remember viscosity Rita condense milk
Modi the best result announcing these are the
favorites in the soil is also coming in the morning
rating was seen Dubai again auto component
Balkrishna Industries 1650 in childhood take
1630 from dreams 17 child 2017 child
1740 target
so in sitting such ICICI Lombard
writing how looking very week and
in insurance also published by vote two
HDFC Life is not bay's 1465 to 70
stoploss 1495 14 Venus target is one
while will give you these the sacrificial things
perfect for 10 minutes all the staff
selection and also in the stocks related to partner conjunction
this role for 593 595 in 582
582 propose target of 1620 Bal Krishna
Industries will retire from
all strong buy in the rally of 1655 place 1630
and  Stoploss and above 1725 1740
1725 1748 Stoploss shot
ICICI Lombard Forces can cover up to 1665
16 inches and Mafia 1473 1495 One
more day's fear after that
settle you better